{
    "subject": "resource/Dalhalla",
    "predicate": "property/hasPhotoCollection",
    "object": "http://wifo5-03.informatik.uni-mannheim.de/flickrwrappr/photos/Dalhalla",
    "human_readable": "Dalhalla has a photo collection.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.985878586769104,
            "question": "Does Dalhalla have a photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9855973124504089,
            "question": "Is there a photo collection associated with Dalhalla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9711005091667175,
            "question": "Does Dalhalla house a collection of photos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9613693356513977,
            "question": "Is there a photographic archive at Dalhalla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9176661372184753,
            "question": "What kind of collection does Dalhalla have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8725990653038025,
            "question": "What can you find in Dalhalla's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8235340714454651,
            "question": "What type of items are found in Dalhalla's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7844220399856567,
            "question": "What is stored in Dalhalla's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7823870778083801,
            "question": "What does Dalhalla specialize in collecting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.761455237865448,
            "question": "What kind of material does Dalhalla collect?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dalhalla has a photo collection.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1122_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does Dalhalla specialize in collecting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1122_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is stored in Dalhalla's collection?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1122_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of items are found in Dalhalla's collection?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1122_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1122_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that one of the documents mentions \"Below is a gallery of photos from Dalhalla.\" which suggests that Dalhalla does have a photo collection."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention \"Below is a gallery of photos from Dalhalla,\" which supports the statement that Dalhalla has a photo collection."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}